Here is my current bio,

Born and raised in Aubagne near Marseille, South of France, I studied agronomy and food engineering. I received a master's degree in industrial Management at AgroTech Paris, Paris France and also a Corporate finance degree at SPS Universidad, Honduras CA.

I have worked for a variety of companies in different fields and countries. During my career I have been a genetic researcher--identifying antibodies for the Chagas disease in Venezuela--, a product manager for Arjo Wiggins in England, a manufacturing manager in the French food industry--as well as deputy General Manager in the food industry in Honduras, Central America. Recently, I have been working for 13 years a major consulting firm 'Capgemini Consulting' and head the Transformation University during 3 years. I led Human aspect of international transformation programs, designed executive development program, facilitated executive workshop, coached executives for clients such as adidas group, Michelin, SEB group, Lafarge, EADS, Orange, Capgemini, Sogeti, Bureau Veritas, TCS, Paris city council, ... etc

I am fluent in French, Spanish and English and have basic knowledge in Arabic and Mandarin. My passion is what I am practicing now in my professional life: coaching and leading the world with open eyes, hunger and a wise heart. I am a Certified Professional Co-Active coach ACC, accredited Co-Active leader, ORSC accredited and MBTI I & II certified practitioner.

I love to create, invent new ways of doing things and work in groups. I have tons of ideas and am ready to jump with excitement into my path. For me, this is at the very core about living fully in all parts of my life into my life purpose, namely to serve people to break free and empower collective creation of beauty and balance in our World/Universe.

My family, my 3 boys and my Corsican roots are my anchor.

Cécile Randoing François

25 rue Victor Hugo 73100 Aix les Bains - France ① +336.63.88.52.52 ☑ cecile.randoing@gmail.com 43 years old



Professional experiences

2011 – 2013 Cappemini Consulting, Paris France

Head of Transformation University™ France

- Business development
- Brand development and communication
- Team management: 10 experienced consultants and a network of specialized freelances
- Development of the Executive Leadership practice:
 - Leadership strategy
 - Culture Change
 - Tailored curriculum design
 - o Facilitation & co-leading of event or training session,
 - Individual and team coaching (top management & executive level)

Client: Adidas group, Orange, Mairie de Paris, Michelin, groupe Seb, Touring Club Suisse, ... etc

2005 – 2010 Capgemini Consulting, Paris France

Led international business and Transformation programs

- Diagnosis (organization, process, management, culture).
- Organization design &implementation and process re-engineering
- Change Management strategy and implementation
- Training design & facilitation

Clients: Lafarge, Go Sport, Bureau Veritas, Scotts Miracle grow, SNCF, ... etc.

2000 – 2004 Capgemini Consulting, Lyon France

Manager of the Employee Transformation profit center: business development, P&L, staffing (20 consultants), mentoring & training.

Clients: Volvo Trucks, Volvo IT, Michelin, GEG, Grenoble University, EADS ... etc

1998 – 2000 Dehydration Technologies, San Pedro Sula, Honduras CA

Deputy General Manager

- Executive Adviser to CEO
- Development of company policies and strategy, Internal audits and diagnosis
- Elaboration of annual budget and capital investment plans
- Transfer of the marketing department from the European headquarters to America HQ.
- Development of a new partnership with US customer for retail sales

1997-1998	Confectionery	Reynaud,	Marseille –	France
-----------	---------------	----------	-------------	--------

Quality and Production Manager

1994-1996 Générale Sucrière, Saint Louis group – Burgundy France

Quality manager (2 factories and a packaging unit)

1993 Arjo Wiggins, Basingstoke UK

Junior Product manager – Fine Paper Marketing department

1991 Biotechnology & genetic laboratory – Cerveceria Polar, Caracas Venezuela

Biology Engineering Intern

Training & Education

- Organization & Relationship Systems Coaching (ORSC) training –Paris, France 2013 (on going)
- Council Guide Training, Bern Switzerland 2012 (on going)
- Myers Briggs Type Indicator level II Certification (MBTI II) Paris, France 2012
- ICF accredited coach (ACC) 2012
- Co-active leadership certification North Carolina, USA 2011
- Certified Professional Co-active Coach (CPCC) Paris, France 2010 / 2012
- Myers Briggs Type Indicator Certification (MBTI) Paris, France 2002
- Project Leader, certification International Engagement Manager Capgemini University 2001
- Extensive training in corporate Finance San Pedro Sula University, Honduras 2000
- AgroTech Paris Engineer Master in Industrial Management with honors Paris, France 1993

Language

French: mother tongue

English & Spanish: professional

Hobbies

Member of the AgroParisTech alumni group "Agro au Féminin" Tai Ji Quan Personal development Blogging